[    
    {
        "title": "Languages",
        "flashcards": [
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in England?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "English"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in Vietnam?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Vietnamese"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in China?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Cantonese"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in France?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "French"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Languages",
        "flashcards": [
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in England?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "English"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in Vietnam?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Vietnamese"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in China?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Cantonese"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in France?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "French"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Languages",
        "flashcards": [
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in England?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "English"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in Vietnam?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Vietnamese"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in China?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Cantonese"
            },
            {
                "question": "What langauge is spoken in France?",
                "answers": [
                    "Vietnamese",
                    "English",
                    "Cantonese",
                    "French"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "French"
            }
        ]
    }
]